PERB Collective Bargaining Agreements from States other than New York 6065
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
PERB Collective Bargaining Agreements from States other than New York
1965- 1977
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Public Employees Relation Board (PERB)
6065
11 cubic feet
11 linear ft.
Agreements.
5791184
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 18, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 18, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5140: NYS PERB Agreements 6257: NYS PERB "The Taylor Law On Its 40th Anniversary" Publication
Collective labor agreements -- United States; Government employees -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- United States
5791184
- Administrative Professional Group of Reno - Agreements (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Alaska Fishermen's Union - Agreements, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Alexandria Police Association (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Attorneys' Association of Torrence (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Auto,Marine&Specialty Painters' Union - Local 1176 - Agreements (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Automotive and Special Services Union - Local 461 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bridgeman's Association of Monmouth County Agreement (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Building and Construction Trade Council of Contra Costa County (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Building and construction Trades Council of Dayton, Ohio - Agreements (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Building and Construction Trade Council of Greater Detroit (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Building and Construction Trades Council of Los Angeles (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Building and Construction Trades Council of Milwaukee Cnty. (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Building and Construction Trades Council - Sacramento-Sierra - Agreements (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Building and Construction Trades Council of Santa Clara and San Benito Counties Agreements (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Building, Plumbing and Electrical Inspectors, Assn. of - Agreements (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Building Trades Council of Allegheny County - Agreement (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Calhoun County Deputies Association (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Carpenter's District Council Local 104, Miami Valley Agreements (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Carpenters and Joiners United Brd. Of Local 79 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Carpenters and Joiners, United Brotherhood of America et. Al. Local 24 - Agreement (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Caseworkers of Cities of Stamford, Dept. of Public Welfare - Agreements (Box 1, Folder 21)
- City Employees' Association (Box 1, Folder 22)
- City Employees' Assn., Sacramento - Agreements (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Civil Service Association, Council 16 of New Jersey - Agreement (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Civil Service Employees Affiliates Waterbury City Employees' Assn. Agreements (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Classified Municipal Employees Assn. Agreement (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Clerical Employees, Local 1 - Agreement (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Colorado River Power Trades Council - Agreements (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Communications Workers of America (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Confidential Employees' Organization (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Contra Costa County Appraiser's Assoc. (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Correction Officers Association Agreement (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Crafts Council of Seattle, Joint Agreements (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Crossing Guards Assn. of the New Haven - Police Dept. Agreements (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Deputy Sheriffs Association of Contra Costa - Agreement (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Deputy Sheriff's Assn., Marin county - Agreement (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Deputy Sheriffs Association - Agreements Santa Clara (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Deputy Sheriff's Association Agreement of Solano County (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Deputy Sheriff's Assn., Washington Cnty. - Agreements (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Deputy Sheriff's Assn. of Yakima County (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Electrical Workers Intl. Brotherhood of Local Agreement (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Electrical Workers, International Brotherhood of Local 77 - Agreement (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Electrical Workers, International Brotherhood of Local 100 - Agreements (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Electrical Workers, International Brotherhood of Local 332 - Agreements (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Electrical Workers, International Brotherhood of Local 483 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Electrical Workers, International Brotherhood of Local 1245 - Agreements (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Employees Association of Calhoun County (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Employees' Association of Clakamas Agreement (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Employees Assn., Fresno City Agreements (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Employees Assn., Kent County - Agreements (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Employees Assn., Los Angeles County - Agreements (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Employees' Assn., Marin County - Agreements (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Employees Assoc. of Outagamie County (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Employees Pierce County and Tacoma City Agreement (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Employees Association of San Joaquin Agreement (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Employees Association of Santa Cruz - Agreement (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Employees Association of Solano County - Agreement (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Employees Association of Sonoma County - Agreement (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Employees Assn. of Torrance City - Agreement (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Employees' Council of the USMV North Star III - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Employees Organization, Sacramento County Agreements (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Engineers' Association of Torrence (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Engineers & Attorneys Assn. of Agreements (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Engineers, Professional and Technical Association of, Local #17 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Engineers, Western Council of (Contra Costa County) (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Federal Employees, National Federation of Local 185 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Five Chief, Assistant of Reno - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Fire Dept., Chief of, Denver - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Fire Dept. Personnel Assn., Alexandria - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Fire Fighters' Assn., Arlington County Professional - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Firefighter's Assn. Eloise - Agreement (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Fire Fighters' Assn., Livonia - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Fire Fighters Assoc., Milwaukee Cnty. (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Fire Fighters, Intl. Assn. of Local 27 - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Fire Fighters, Intl. Assn. of Local 29 - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Fire Fighters, Intl. Assn. of Local 31 - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Fire Fighters, Intl. Assn. of Local 36 - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Fire Fighters, Int'l Assn. of Local 42 - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Fire Fighters, Intl. Assn. of Local 136 - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Fire Fighters, Intl. Assn. of Local 302 - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Fire Fighters, Intl. Assn. of Local 311 - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Fire Fighters, Intl. Assn. of Local 366 - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Fire Fighters, Intl. Assn. of Local 385, Omaha Assn. of Firefighters Agreements (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Fire Fighters, Intl. Assn. of Local 505 Agreements (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Firefighters, Intl. Assn. of Local 522, Sacramento Fire Fighters (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Firefighters, Intl. Assn. of AFL-CIO Local 574 - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Firefighters, International Assoc. of, Local 731 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Firefighters Intl. Assn. of Local 734 - Agreement (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Firefighters, Intl. Assn. Local 747 Agreements (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Firefighters, Intl. Assn. of AFL-CIO Local 753 - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Firefighters, Intl. Assn. of Local 760 - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Firefighters, Intl. Assn. of Local 825 - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Firefighters, Intl. Assn. of Local 858 - Agreement (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Firefighters, Intl. Assn. of Local 873, San Jose Firefighting Assn. - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Firefighters Intl. Assn. of Local 964 - Agreement (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Firefighters, Intl. Assn. of Local 1014 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Firefighters - Intl. Assoc. of Local 1064, IAFF Agreements AFL-CIO (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Firefighters, Intl. Assn. of Local 1066 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Firefighters, International Assoc. of AFL-CIO, Local 1072 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Fire Fighters International Association of Local 1138 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Firefighters, Intl. Assn. of Local 1227 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Fire Fighters International Association of, Local 1230 - Agreement (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Fire Fighters, International Association of, Local 1285 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Fire Fighters, International Association of, Local 1612 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Fire Fighters International Association of, Local 1617 - Agreement (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Firefighters, Intl. Brotherhood Local 1619 - Agreement (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Fire Fighters, International Association of, Local 1834 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Fire Fighters International Association of Local 1908 - Agreement (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Fire Fighters' Association of Torrence (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Fire Fighters of Los Angeles County - Local 1014 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Fire Fighters of Los Angeles County - Local 1014 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Fire Fighters, Intl Assoc. of Local 2068 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Firefighters Intl. Assn. Local 2141 - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Firefighters, Intl. Assn. Local 2294 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Firefighters Union Local 891 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Firemen and Oilers, International of Local Agreement (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Firemen's Assn., Huntington Beach - Agreements (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Firemen and Oilers, Intl. Brotherhood of Local 32 - Agreements (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Firemen and Oilers, International Brotherhood of Local 63 - Agreement (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Firemen and Oilers, Intl Brotherhood of AFL-CIO, Local 1220 - Agreements (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Food Service Association of Anchorage School - Agreement (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Government Bar Association, Wayne County - Agreements (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Government Employees, Amer. Fed. Of Local 872 - Agreements (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Government Employees, Amer. Fed. Of Local 1550 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Government Employees, American Federation of, Local 2330, Internal Revenue (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Government Employees, Amer. Fed. Of Local 2553 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Hotel, Motel, Restaurant Employees, Cooks and Bartenders Union, Local 24 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders Union, Local 217 - Agreements (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders Intl. Union, Local 234 - Agreement (Box 3, Folder 16)
- House Staff Assn. of the Santa Clara Valley Medical Center - Agreements (Box 3, Folder 17)
- International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge no. 437 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Internal Revenue Employees, National Association Of (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Interns and Residents Physicians Employee Representation Unit (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Jersey City Public Employees, Local 245 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Jersey City School Traffic Guards - Assoc. - Agreements (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Joint Crafts of King County, Washington - Agreements (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Joint Crafts Council of Seattle - Agreement (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Joint Labor Committee of Tacoma (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Journeymen, Barbers, Hair Dressers, Cosmetologists and Proprietors, Intl. Local 552 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Laborers' International Union, Local 61 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Laborers Intl. Union of N.A. Local 236 - Agreements (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Laborers' Intl. Union of North America - Agreement (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Laborers Intl. Union Local 301 - Agreements (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Laborer's Int'l Union of North America Local 483 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Las Vegas City Employees' Protective and Benefit Association, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Letter Carriers Natl. Assn. of Agreements (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Letter Carriers, Natl. Assn. of Agreements (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Library Employees Association (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Machinists & Aerospace Workers, Intl Assoc. of District #10 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Machinist & Aerospace Workers, Intl Assoc. of Dist. Council 60, Local 82 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Intl. Assoc. of District 160 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Machinists and Aerospace Workers, International Association of Local 1060 - Agreement (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Management Employees' Organization Huntington Beach Agreements (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Management Employees (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of N.A., AFL-CIO Local 26 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Municipal Employees Assn. of Reno - Agreements (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Municipal Employees' Local 117 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Nurses Association of California - Agreements (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Nurses Assn., Maryland Baltimore City Hospitals' Chapters Agreement (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Nurses Association, Connecticut - Agreements (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Licensed Practical Nurses Assn. of the Cook County School of Nursing (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Delaware Nurses' Assn. - Agreements (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Nurses Association of Hawaii - Agreement (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Nurses Assoc. of Maryland (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Nurses Assoc. of Michigan - Agreements (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Nurses - Staff Nurses Council of Milwaukee (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Licensed Practical Nurses Assn. - Multnomah Cnty. - Agreement (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Nurses Association of Oregon - Agreement (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Nurses Association of Pennsylvania - Agreement (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Nurses Assn., Washington State - Agreement (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Nurses Organization of Jersey City, United - Agreements (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Nurses Assn. of Wisconsin - Agreement (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Operating Engineers, Intl. Union of Local 3 - Agreement (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Operating Engineers International Union of Local 6-6A-6-6B - Agreement (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Operating Engineers, Intl. Union of Local 20 - Agreements (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Operating Engineers, International Union, Local 34 - Agreements (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Operating Engineers, International Union of Local 39 - Agreements (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Operating Engineers, Intl. Union of Stationary Local 39 - Agreements (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Operating Engineers, Intl. Union of Local #49 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Operating Engineers, Intl. Union Local 68-68A Agreements (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Operating Engineers Intl. Union of Local 87 - Agreement (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Operating Engineers, Local 95-95A - Agreement (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Operating Engineers, Local #286 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Operating Engineers, Local 501 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Operating Engineers, Intl. Union of. Local 547 - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of Amer. Council 55 - Agreement (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Peace Officers Assn. San Jose - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Plumbing and Pipefitting Ind., Journeymen and Apprentices of. Local 447 - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Police Beneficiary Assn., Arlington County (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Police Benevolent Assn. Pinellas County - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Police - Jersey City Police Officers Benevolent Assoc. - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Police Assn. of Fresno Park - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Police Benevolent Association, Local 77 - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Police Benevolent Association, Local 167 - Agreement (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Police Civilian Employees Assn. - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Police - Deputy Sheriffs' Assoc. Milwaukee Cnty. (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Police, Fraternal Order of. Lodge 1 - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Police, Fraternal Order of. Sunshine City Lodge 4 Agreements (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Police, Fraternal Order of Lodge #5 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Police, Fraternal Order of. Queen City Lodge 10 - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Police, Fraternal Order of. Lodge 28, Youngstown Fraternal Order of Police - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Police, Fraternal Order of Lodge 44 - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Police, Fraternal Order of Lodge 89 - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Police, Fraternal Order of. Lodge 97 - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Police, Fraternal Order of Saginaw Lodge 105 - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Police - Fraternal Order of Police Supervisory Div. - Lodge #141 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Police, Fraternal Order of. Lodge No. 530 - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Police Guild, Spokane - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Police, Lieutenants & Sergeants Assn., Livonia - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Police - Macon County Sheriffs (AFSCME) Local 1894 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Police - Minnesota Teamsters Public Law Enforcement Employees Union, 320 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Police Officers Assn., Livonia - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Police Officers' Assn., Huntington Beach - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Police Officers' Assn., Sacramento - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Police Officers Assn. (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Police Officers Association of Washington - County Agreements (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Police Officers, Intl Brotherhood of Local 308 - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Police Officers' Guild, Seattle - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Police - Patrolmen's Benevolent Assoc. N.J. Weights & Measures, Local 203 - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Reno Police Protective Association (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Police Protective Association of Reno - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Police Relief Assn. of Fresno - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Police - Sheriff's Office Employees Association (Somona County) (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Police Superior Officers Assn. Jersey City - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Police,Tacoma Local 22x - Agreement (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Police Union Local 1, Omaha - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Policemen's Assn., Madison Professional - Agreements (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Prison Employees Independent Union - Agreement (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Probation Association of New Jersey - Agreement (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Professional Employees - ASCP Medical Technologists (Wayne Cnty Branch) (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Professional Employees, California Assoc. of (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Professional Employees - Dietitian and Nutritionist Assoc. of Wayne Cnty (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Professional Employees - Jt. Council of Intern Resident Alumni (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Professional Employees - Milwaukee County Attorneys (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Professional Employees - Technicians Engineers and Architects of Milwaukee (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Professional & Technical Engineers Assn. Local 17 - Agreements (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Professional Peace Officers (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Professional Policemen's Protective Assn. - Agreements (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Professional and Supervisory Association (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Professional and Technical Engineers, Intl Fed. Of Local 17 - Agreements (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Public Employees, Calif. Assoc. of (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Public Employees Assn. of San Bernardino - Agreements (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Public Employees Association of Ventura County - Agreement (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Public Employees, Jersey City Local 245 - Agreements (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Public Employees Inc. of Jersey City Local 246 - Agreements (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Public Employees, United (Berkeley, Calif. Local 390 - Agreements (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Public Service Employees', Local 1300 - Agreements (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Railroad Yardmaster of America - Agreements (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Registered Nurses High Ridge Hospital (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Registered Nurses Staff Council, County of Kent. - Agreements (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Road Employees of Snohomish County Local 109 - Agreement (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Safety Members Association of Ventura County - Agreement (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Saginaw Municipal Employees Club (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Santa Clara County Environmental Health Association - Agreements (Box 6, Folder 23)
- School Dental Hygienists Assn., Stamford - Agreements (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Service Employees International Union - Agreement of Allegheny County (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Service Employees International Union, Local #38 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Service Employees Intl. Union Local 150 - Agreements (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Service Employee Intl. Union, Local 227 AFL-CIO - Agreements (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Service Employees Intl. Union Local 390, United Public Employees (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Service Employees, Intl. Union Local 395 - Agreements (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Service Employees International Union Local 434, Los Angeles County Employees Association (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Service Employees International Union, Local 434/Los Angeles County Employees Association SEIU Local 660 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Service Employees Intl. Union Local 466 - Agreements (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Service Employees Intl. Union Local 495 United Municipal Employees Agreements (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Service Employees International Union Local 535 - Agreements (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Service Employees International Union - Local 602 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Service Employees International Union Local 660 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- State County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of. Local 268 - Agreements (Box 7, Folder 1)
- State County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of Local 270 Washington State Council of County & City Employees - Agreements (Box 7, Folder 2)
- State County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of. Local 278 - Agreements Council 32 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- State County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of Local 287 Board of Education Employees - Agreements (Box 7, Folder 4)
- State, County and Municipal Employees AFL-CIO, Local 310 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Fed. Of. Local 342 - Agreements (Box 7, Folder 6)
- State, County and Municipal Employees Amer. Fed. Of Council 75, Local 350 - Agreement (Box 7, Folder 7)
- State, County & Municipal Employees Local 353, Waterbury City Employees, Agreements (Box 7, Folder 8)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 369 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of District Council 37 Local 371, Social Service Employees Union Agreements (Box 7, Folder 10)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Local 449, Tucson Municipal Employees - Agreement (Box 7, Folder 11)
- State, County and Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of. Council 81, Local 459 - Agreement (Box 7, Folder 12)
- State, County and Municipal Employees American Fed. Of Council 41 - Agreement (Box 7, Folder 13)
- State, County, and Municipal Employees American Fed. Of Local 500 - Agreements (Box 7, Folder 14)
- State, County, & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of. Council 15 Local 530 New Haven Police Union - Agreements (Box 7, Folder 15)
- State, County & Municipal Employees Local 552 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, American Federation of, Local 575 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of Local 646 - Agreement (Box 7, Folder 18)
- State, County, Municipal Emp. Local 685 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- State, County & Employees, Assn. Fed. Of Local 713 - Agreements (Box 7, Folder 20)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of. Local 765 - Agreements (Box 7, Folder 21)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of. Local 802 - Agreements (Box 7, Folder 22)
- State, County and Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of Local 829 - Agreement (Box 7, Folder 23)
- State, County & Municipal Employees Amer. Fed. Of. Local 884 - Agreements (Box 7, Folder 24)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of Dist. Council 51, Local 905 - Agreements (Box 7, Folder 25)
- State, County & Municipal Employees Local 977 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- State, County and Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of. Council 44 - Agreements (Box 7, Folder 27)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of. Local 1048 - Agreements (Box 7, Folder 28)